Alaa Jerbi

Front-End Engineer

Front-End Engineer with experience in application development and design. Fluent in English with excellent writing and verbal skills. Passionate about building products that are not only useful but also delightful to look at and use. Energetic and motivated with strong work ethic in team or individual settings.



Frontend

JS/ES6, Vue, Vuex, React, React Native, Tailwind, Material UI, Bootstrap, HTML5, CSS3

Testing/DevOps

Git, Storybook, Jest, React Testing Library, AWS, Docker, Heroku, Linux

Backend/Database

Node, ExpressJS, Python, Java, MongoDB, SQL, GraphQL

UX Design

Adobe XD, Figma, InVision Studio, Zeplin

WORK EXPERIENCE

Junior Frontend Engineer, Holidu GmbH ☑

 Implemented and maintained features for company's B2B web solutions with React/TypeScript and Material UI.

Jan 2023 - present Munich, Germany

Nov 2021 - Jul 2022

Designed prototypes to improve user experience with Figma.

Junior Front End Engineer, iObeya

• Worked with a team of senior developers to bootstrap the company's newest project

- Developed the project frontend Vue application and participated in the architecture and state management decisions
- Collaborated with design team to build a design system library in Storybook

Software Engineering Intern, iObeya □

Feb 2021 - Aug 2021

- Designed and built a web plugin for recording Snapshot test scenarios
- Built a mechanism for generating automation scripts in Cypress and Selenium
- Built a mechanism to resolve Snapshot regressions

Mobile Developer Intern, PYNTOPYN Technologies ☑

Mar 2020 - Aug 2020

- Built a food scanning mobile app with React Native and Expo SDK
- Built prototype design with InVision Studio

Front End Developer Intern, Kollab Agency

Jul 2019 - Sep 2019

- Built prototype design for an e-wallet mobile application using Adobe XD
- Applied UI Design principles to improve app usability and user experience
- Converted design to HTML and CSS components

EDUCATION

Software Engineering Degree, minor in DevOps,

2016 - 2021

National Institute of Applied Sciences and Technology 2

Baccalaureate in Computer Science, Farhat Hached High School

2012 - 2016

Graduated with honors and highest average in the region.